# PAWEŁ PINDEL

Zachodnia 25, Kraków · +48 884 044 077

pawel.pindel@netsharpdev.com · linkedIn: @pawelpindel · https://netsharpdev.com

My name is Paweł Pindel, I am Software Engineer from Poland, owner of NETSharp Development, currently working for Talmundo. As a developer I have over 4 years of professional experience. I am Microsoft Technologies enthusiast but also open for other tech stacks. Trying to pick language adequate to the problem - not to solve all problems with one language or framework. Blogger at https://netsharpdev.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 01.2017 - CURRENTLY

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPMETN ENGINEER, TALMUNDO**

As a Software Development Engineer at Talmundo, I am responsible for development, maintenance (including DevOps) of infrastructure and architecture of our main product - Onboarding App. Technologies I use in my job are following: .NET Core, ASP.NET MVC, Vue.js, Razor, HTML, CSS and Microsoft Azure.

### **06.2016 - CURRENTLY**

#### OWNER/BLOGGER/DEVELOPER, NETSHARP DEVELOPMENT

Within NETSharp Development I am cooperating with NGOs, small companies and startup delivering them a wide range of services, starting from small websites, dedicated apps, and consultancy. Technologies I use depend on what problem needs to be solved, but mainly I focus on Microsoft technologies. I am co-creator of IqScreen app – the Polish Innovation 2019 prize winner.

#### 06.2016 - 12.2016

## **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, PCMI CORPORATION**

In PCMI corporation I was responsible for the maintenance and development of CRM app for Car Dealers and Insurance Companies. Technologies I was using: ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web Forms, SQL, ADO.NET, AngularJS.

#### 07.2015 - 05.2016

#### **JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, 96VOLT**

In there I gained my first commercial experience. I was developing an ERP system compatible with polish labor law. I was also involved in contact with the customers while we were planning new features. Technologies used: ASP.NET Web Forms, EXT JS 3.4.

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021

**BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING,** WYŻSZA SZKOŁA EKONOMII I INFORMATYKI W KRAKOWIE (WSEI)

2014 - 2017

AGH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

# **SKILLS**

- 4,5 years of experience in ASP.NET/.NET Core
- Basic knowledge of frontend frameworks Angular 2+, Vue.js
- Git

- Experience in Azure Cloud
- Experience in Azure DevOps
- Knowledge about ORMs: Entity Framework Core, Dapper
- Experience in SQL server

# **ACTIVITIES**

My motto is: "Try to learn something about everything and everything about something." — Thomas Henry Huxley

Besides development, I am amateur chef and really enjoy travelling and hiking around the world but especially in love with polish countryside and nature. In my free time I train archery.